<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bakeys Diet Food</string>
    <string name="japan_diet_name">Japanese diet</string>
    <string name="japan_diet_desc">A distinctive feature of this method is a high rate of weight loss: you will become lighter by 7 to 10 kilograms in 13-14 days. The effectiveness of the Japanese diet is achieved through a complete restructuring of your metabolism. In this case, the result obtained remains for at least two years. It is forbidden to drink alcohol, sugar, salt, cakes, and sweets while keeping a diet. The Japanese weight loss program is considered to be low-calorie, its diet focuses on low-carbohydrate foods, due to which the body must burn stored fat to produce energy. During following the method, the stomach shrinks in size, which facilitates the process of leaving it.
    Another important condition: you should eat slowly, chewing your food thoroughly, without distractions such as movies, TV shows, and other entertainment. You should be completely focused on your meal, then your body will feel full faster.</string>
    <string name="dukan_diet_name">Dukan diet</string>
    <string name="dukan_diet_desc">This is a protein diet program. The duration of the diet depends on the amount of excess weight and reaches 3 - 4 months. The DuCan methodology is divided into four stages: "Ataka", "Chedding", "Consolidation" and "Stabilization", each of which has its own diet, duration, allowed and prohibited products to eat. General requirements of the diet: do daily morning exercise, add oat bran to meals, walk outside for at least half an hour. The DuCan weight loss scheme does not limit the amount of consumed "allowed" products, excludes the use of chemical additives, drugs and is considered safe to follow.
    Ducan argued that a large amount of protein in the diet helps to normalize weight. After all, protein is low in calories, and digesting it, the body uses more energy than when consuming carbohydrates. As a result, fat is burned.
    By restricting yourself from consuming carbohydrates and fats, the body goes into a state similar to starvation and uses up the fat reserves in the body.</string>
    <string name="grechka_diet_name">Buckwheat diet</string>
    <string name="grechka_diet_desc">It belongs to the category of hard mono-diet, designed for rapid weight loss. The main ingredient of the method is buckwheat, which must be prepared according to a special technology. It is forbidden to boil buckwheat, fill it with boiling water and insist for eight hours. At the same time, it is not allowed to add seasonings and salt. After this time, buckwheat porridge can be eaten in unlimited quantities. The classical version of the diet is designed for one week (weight loss makes up 4-5 kilograms during this period), it is possible to extend it to 14 days (minus 6-10 kilograms). While losing weight, in addition to buckwheat it is allowed to drink 1.5 liters of alkaline mineral water, green tea and a liter of kefir with a fat content of 1%.
        You should eat 150 to 250 grams of dried buckwheat per day. Green or brown groats should not be boiled, but boiled. For this purpose, one part of buckwheat is poured into 2.5 parts of boiling water and the container is closed, wrapped in a towel. Overnight the groats will be ready, and the vitamins in them will not be destroyed. In this case salt, sugar, spices are completely excluded, that is, buckwheat is eaten "empty". If it is hard to chew, it is allowed to mix buckwheat with nonfat kefir.
        There are four meals, the main ones in the morning until 5 or 6 p.m. It is obligatory to drink a lot of water and take multivitamins.
     If you feel worsened while following the method, it is recommended to introduce non-caloric fruits (apples, oranges, grapefruit) into your daily diet.</string>
    <string name="belok_diet_name">A protein diet</string>
    <string name="belok_diet_desc">The main rule of the method is that 85% of the menu of a person who is losing weight should consist of protein products: lean meat, fish, eggs, dairy products, and seafood. This is an effective diet for 2 weeks, which will help to get rid of 4 - 8 extra pounds during this period. The principle of the protein day: eat small portions every three hours. It is allowed to enter into the daily diet of carbohydrate products with a low glycemic index (up to 40): soy, cucumbers, nuts, mashed chickpeas, citrus fruits.
    To lose weight quickly and increase muscle mass, it is recommended to perform strength exercises.
    It is best to make a menu in advance, to go shopping for groceries. Try not to have unnecessary products in the refrigerator, which could negate the efforts made. The main condition is that the protein diet should be accompanied by physical activity. Even if you are not engaged in sports, it is worth to start exercising, running, cycling every day or at least every other day.</string>
    <string name="maggi_diet_name">The Maggie Diet</string>
    <string name="maggi_diet_desc">Designed to eliminate 10 to 20 pounds in four weeks. The Maggi method includes the following most effective diets: cottage cheese and egg. What option to give preference to depends on personal eating habits and health conditions. Both options are effective. The Maggi diet is not a mono-diet, its ration includes vegetables, fruits and meat. The products are chosen in such a way as to activate the burning of accumulated fat and remove toxins from the body.
    The menu of the egg diet Maggi is quite sparse in variety, so be prepared that you will have to eat the same things. But the result is worth it. Note that you can eat as much as you want from the menu, which has no portion weight.
    On the Maggi diet, at least 2 liters of water should be consumed daily. You are allowed to drink coffee and tea without sugar and milk at any time, regardless of meals. Below is a menu designed for 4 weeks.</string>
    <string name="keto_diet_name">The keto diet</string>
    <string name="keto_diet_desc">After the complete rejection of carbohydrates on about 2-3 days, blood sugar levels drop to minimum values, and the body switches to ketosis mode, starting to use the energy of fat deposits for the needs of the current metabolism.
    Originally, the keto diet, which puts the body into ketosis mode, was used to treat chronic diseases, but now it is one of the most popular for weight loss. The advantage of the keto diet is that it does not require calorie counting and does not cause feelings of hunger - you just need to eliminate carbohydrates completely.
    The disadvantages include the monotony of the diet and the difficulty of choosing dishes when eating out - the menus of most canteens and restaurants have an extremely limited number of carbohydrate-free options (for example, even cutlets may contain carbohydrates in the form of breading).</string>
    <string name="kefir_diet_name">Kefir diet</string>
    <string name="kefir_diet_desc"> This is a strict weight loss methodology that is popular nowadays. There are the following light versions of the sour milk diet: kefir-cottage, kefir-apple, kefir-egg, kefir-wheat, kefir-cucumber, streaky. When following the strict method, the only product allowed to be consumed is non-fat kefir or 1%. You must drink a liter of fermented milk drink in five meals per day. During the breaks drink water, at least 1.5 liters per day. After three "kefir" days you will become lighter by 1.5 kilograms, after a week - by 3, for 14 days - up to 8.
        Kefir is quite nutritious and the feeling of hunger will not be so strong. A large amount of calcium is good for your bones, nails, and teeth.
        This diet is one of the most effective, and the result will be visible in a few days.
        To avoid an increase in the secretion of gastric juice, the development of gastritis, worsening ulcers to practice a strict fermented milk diet for more than two weeks is not recommended.</string>
    <string name="sredizemnoe_diet_name">The Mediterranean diet</string>
    <string name="sredizemnoe_diet_desc">The menu is characterized by a large amount of lean fish and seafood, 4-6 times a week. Fish replaces the usual fried cutlets and pork, which are prohibited. You can eat lean beef, chicken, turkey and rabbit. Also increase the amount of dairy products without additives with a low percentage of fat. Dairy products and fruit can be eaten every day, but only unsweetened. Simple carbohydrates - sweets and sugar, are replaced by complex: pasta from whole grain cereals, coarse bread, cereals. Fatty hard cheeses are replaced by low-fat cheeses - mozzarella, cottage cheese.
        Potatoes and sweet fruits like bananas should be very limited. Alcohol, fatty and spicy foods are forbidden. Only dry wine, not more than a glass a day, is allowed.
        The Mediterranean diet is presented as a food pyramid. The pyramid is based on fruits, vegetables, nuts, pasta, bread, and cereals. Each person should eat at least five servings of fruits and vegetables per day. Bread and cereals should be chosen from whole grains. White bread and rice should be abstained from. Bread is very popular in the Mediterranean countries, but they eat it without any additives, just dipping it in olive oil. No sausage and butter sandwiches.</string>
</resources>